Copyright © 2010-2013 SourceGear, LLC

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.

--

Yep, that's our copyright notice. Now here's a todo list.

Todo:
 - Eat lunch in a café.
 - Polish up resumé.
 - Stop being so naïve.
 - Modify a line of text.
 - Add a line of text.
 - Delete a line of text.
 - Whatever.
 - And stuff.

The end.
